that's how it is, thank you, yes, yes
okay Hör will come in and lay eggs then
Of course. Do you have any questions about it? No
you know what a pitched roof is then No, but I do
will give you good advice take care and
so angry when we said he had
milked too little but I think he is
quite out of phase and that dude without
sleep coffee eh sleep he will now be right
unpleasant this breakfast will come enough
nothing but it is like He alone
waiting for things to be done and
he has stayed in the kitchen and so on
that I don't think he's feeling well right now
now, but he'll probably have to bite the bullet and toughen up
out to
at least after the next big ball or
fight fairer
said Good job Me all Yes new day
the idea is perhaps that we can be finished
today and then chill a bit tomorrow